<package>
	<id>com.jammytea.stencilborders</id>
	<name>Stencil borders</name>
	<version>1.0</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>7.0</miniOS>
			<otherVersions>unconfirmed</otherVersions>
			<!--
			for otherVersions, you can put either unsupported or unconfirmed
			-->
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies></dependencies>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description>The most customisable theme around just got bigger.</description>
		<description>Designed to perfectly match the Stencil themes, this is a set of 13 icon borders and folder icons/backgrounds so you can personalise the theme even further - pair a border outline of one colour with an icon set of another. But they also look great with any other glyph themes</description>
		<description>Included are sets to match each variant of Stencil, with black, white, the full set of Spectrum colours, and two special new rainbow styles.</description>
		<description>Although they were designed to frame the glyph sets, they work just as well with the outlined icon versions, so you can use the standard, multicoloured icons but all framed in the same colour, to really tie your Springboard together.</description>
		<description>Stacking makes a difference too - put the icon theme to the top to remove folders, put your border to the top to theme your folder the same as the icons, or put a folder theme to the top to have a different colour. With Snowboard (for which you need the Icon Effects Extension), you can also pair the borders with one of the backgrounds from Stencil Backgrounds (downloaded separately) for even more possibilities.</description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>	<screenshot>
			<image>1.jpg</image>
		</screenshot><screenshot>
				<image>2.jpg</image>
			</screenshot>
			<screenshot>
					<image>3.jpg</image>
				</screenshot><screenshot>
						<image>4.jpg</image>
					</screenshot>
					<screenshot>
							<image>5.jpg</image>
						</screenshot>
						<screenshot>
								<image>6.jpg</image>
							</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change>Initial release</change>
	</changelog>
	<links></links>
</package>
